A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, Office of the President, Office Files of H. Rowan Gaither FA621
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Administration, 1947-1959; VI; 1.9 Cubic Feet 5 letter document boxes
  - Public Relations, 1949-1959; E
    - Hearst Press, 1953 July-September (Box 11, Folder 135)
    - Rep. Donald L. Jackson, 1953 March-April (Box 11, Folder 136)
    - Joint Congressional Committee on Internal Revenue Taxation, 1954 November-December (Box 11, Folder 137)
    - Lewis, Fulton, 1952 December-1953 August (Box 11, Folder 138)
    - McCarran Rider, 1952 December-1954 October (Box 11, Folder 139)
    - Sen. Joseph R. McCarthy, 1953 March-May (Box 12, Folder 140)
    - Other Foundations and Non-Profit Groups, 1949 June-1958 April (Box 12, Folder 141)
    - Press Releases, circa 1953 (Box 12, Folder 142)
    - Press Releases, 1954 February-June (Box 12, Folder 143)
    - Press Releases, 1954 July-1956 July (Box 12, Folder 144)
    - Press Releases, 1953 August-1956 October (Box 12, Folder 145)
    - Publications, 1953 December-1956 January (Box 12, Folder 146)
    - Reece Committee, 1954 July-1955 July (Box 12, Folder 147)
    - Representative Frank Thompson Jr., 1955 July-1956 March (Box 12, Folder 148)
    - Treasury Department, 1954 November-1956 March (Box 12, Folder 149)
- Non-Program Suggestions, 1952-1956; VII; 0.38 Cubic Feet 1 letter document box
  The material consists of program proposals which were not funded, and funded projects that did not fall under the usual program areas.
  - Atomic Energy, 1954 March-1956 March (Box 13, Folder 150)
  - Canadian Projects, 1956 May-September (Box 13, Folder 151)
  - Cultural Affairs, 1954 February-September (Box 13, Folder 152)
  - General, 1954 October-1956 March (Box 13, Folder 153)
  - Institutional Support, 1953 November-1956 May (Box 13, Folder 154)
  - National Security Research, 1955 June-1956 February (Box 13, Folder 155)
  - Natural Sciences, 1952 November-1954 December (Box 13, Folder 156)
  - Natural Sciences, 1954 February-1956 May (Box 13, Folder 157)
  - Salk [Polio] Vaccine Information, 1955 May (Box 13, Folder 158)
- Ford Motor Company Reports, 1933-1956; VIII; 0.62 Cubic Feet 1 letter document box and 1 half-legal box
  Annual and financial reports arranged chronologically.
  - Ford Motor Company - Annual Reports, 1946-1949 (Box 14, Folder 159)
  - Ford Motor Company - 1950 Annual Report and Special Supplement to 1950 Annual Report (Box 14, Folder 160)
  - Ford Motor Company - 1951 Annual Report and Special Supplement to 1951 Annual Report (Box 14, Folder 161)
  - Ford Motor Company - 1952 Annual Report and Special Supplement to 1952 Annual Report (Box 14, Folder 162)
  - Ford Motor Company - 1953 Annual Report and Special Supplement to 1953 Annual Report (Box 14, Folder 163)
  - Ford Motor Company - 1954 Annual Report and Special Supplement to 1954 Annual Report (Box 14, Folder 164)
  - Ford Motor Company - Annual Reports, 1955-1956 (Box 14, Folder 165)
  - Ford Motor Company - Aduit and Compensation Commttee File: Supplemental Compensation Plan adopted July 14, 1950. August 1950. (Box 14, Folder 166)
  - Ford Motor Company Quarerly Reports, March. 31, 1952 - September 3, 1955., 1952-1955 (Box 14, Folder 167)
  - Composite Registration Statement, Securities and Exchange Commssion, Form S-1 Registration Statement under the Securities Act of 1933., 1956 (Box 15, Folder 168)